hey folks David to with Barb ben.com and
today we're talking about how to watch
the 2023 Olympia weekend now this is a
pay-per-view so you are going to have to
Shell out if you want to watch all the
coverage video wise live we're going to
have plenty of written coverage on
barandcross continue bringing you the
news from around the world of strength
and if you don't want to watch this full
video that's okay I might not want to
watch me either make sure to click on
the link in the description below where
we have all the details on how to watch
so the first and best option to watch
the 2023 Olympia weekend that's all
divisions from bikini to figure to
Wellness to Classic physique to men's
open wheelchair you name it well that's
going to be the Olympia 2023 premium
pay-per-view package which is available
at Olympia productions.com that's going
to cost about 75 bucks for the entire
weekend and we'll bring you the live
stream with everything they're actually
recording and streaming from the Olympia
weekend it's actually what we'll be
subscribing to at barbend to follow
along now that premium subscription it's
not cheap 75 bucks for a weekend of
content that's a lot of cash now again
75 bucks for a weekend of content might
seem like a lot but that premium package
also gets you replays on demand from the
last few years of the Olympia weekend so
there is some additional value there
Beyond just this year's live stream keep
that in mind now there is a free stream
on something called The Fan Channel you
may still have to register at Olympia
productions.com But it includes the 2023
Olympia press conference the Expo and
something called meet the Olympians
we're not sure exactly what form that'll
take this year but it'll be some pseudo
behind the scenes or sit down interview
content with some of the top competitors
again there is a free version bring you
some of the content but that's not going
to get you the live coverage that you
might be looking for it's not going to
give you call outs it's not going to
give you pose Downs it's not going to
give you ultimately when they list off
the winners on stage and athletes get
emotional and they're so happy and then
they pretend to be happy for each other
because they didn't win but they all
worked really hard that sort of thing
you're going to have to pay for that to
watch that live and again that's the
pay-per-view premium option which is
about
$75 but no matter what you do we're
going to have plenty of written live
coverage at Barb .c so we won't leave
you hanging there we always enjoy the
Olympia weekend and bringing you that
content until then I'm David to thanks
for tuning
[Music]
in